ANAND L

Data Analyst / Senior Data Process Associate

I have experience more than 10 years in small start-up business environments. Effective driver of product development lifecycle from concept to delivery. Communicative and collaborative with proven history of improving business operations to support corporate growth and revenue. Detail-oriented team player with strong organizational skills. Ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously with a high degree of accuracy.



CONTACT

Phone: +91 9566855101

Email: 19and1991@gmail.com Address: Tirunelveli, Tamil Nadu

EDUCATION

St Johns College, Tirunelveli June 2008 - May 2011 B.Sc. Computer Science Alagappa University, Tirunelveli August 2016 - May 2018 M.Sc. Psychology

Hindi

WORK EXPERIENCE

Annap Interactive Solution Private Limited - Data Process Associate

Dec 2012 - Dec 2022

MS Excel (Pivot Table, Formulae, VBA Macros, Tools) Power Query Editor Google Spreadsheet Worked in E-Commerce Website, OpenCart, WordPress, Data Process/Update in Website vicky.in, spicyonion.com, cellbharat.com

BrandM Solutions Private Limited - Data Analyst / Senior Data Process Associate

English

January 2021 - Current

MS Excel (Pivot Table, Formulae, VBA Macros, Tools) Power Query Editor, Google Spreadsheet, Lead Customer Relationship Management, Team Lead (15 Tele Callers and Manage Leads Process), Data Studio Tool, Power BI, MySQL, Python (Beginner)

SKILLS

Tamil

